

Contact



Minsk, Belarus



+375445863944



zlotnik.ilya1994@gmail.com

About me

I Front-End Developer with experience 1 years of in creating SPA using React (JS/TS), Redux. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies, such as studying React Native.

Applying new stack technologies does not cause difficulties. Constantly self-learning in different online platforms such as Codewars, Udemy, YouTube, reading IT-literature and improve my English.

Open for your suggestions.

Skills

- React/Redux
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Storybook
- Unit test
- Formik
- REST API

- Redux Toolkit
- HTML/CSS/SASS
- Node.js
- GitHub
- Figma
- Material-Ul

Languages

- Russia native
- English A2 in progress

Zlotnik Ilya

Front-end developer











Work Experience

My Project as Frontend (2022-Present) developer (Part-time)

• Cards

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, SCSS, React, Redux Toolkit, Reduxthunk, Axios, Formik, Material UI, Yap, Refactoring, Deploying; React Hook; React-Router-dom.

TODOLIST

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, React-router-dom, Axios, Formik, Material UI; Refactoring, bug fixing, Deploying, Covering code with unit tests;

• SOCIAL NETWORK

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, React, Redux, Redux-thunk, Axios, React Hook, Deploying, organizing correct app architecture;

Key responsibilities on my projects

- Increase in productivity Form processing
- Bug fixing
- Teamwork
- Refactoring
- Unit testing, storybook
- · Creating an atorization and registration flow on React + Redux + Axios

Lead Engineer(Full-time) (2017-2022)

- Working with normative and technical documentation;
- Team management
- · Development of technical documentation;
- · Quality control of works and technologies;
- Development and implementation of technologies
- · Commissioning of equipment, tools;
- · Work with providers;

Education

IT-INCUBATOR | (2022-2023)

Front-end developer (HTML, CSS, JS, Git, TS, React, React-Native, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Formik, REST API, Storybook, TDD, Unit test)

THE ROLLING SCOPES SCHOOL | (2021 - 2022)

Front-end developer (HTML, CSS, JS, Git, TS)

BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY (2011-2016)

Engineer, Economist-manager